Laxmi Pragna Varun Pillalamarri

pillalamarrivarun@gmail.com

9390310423

linkedin.com/in/varun-pillalamarri

Summary

Skilled multitasker with superior work ethic and good teamwork, problem-solving and organizational skills. Willing to take on any task to help team. Reliable and dedicated team player with hardworking and resourceful approach. Hardworking Student good work experience as intern and extensive knowledge of core subject matter. Meticulous and detail-oriented with excellent observational, organizational and communication skills

Experience



Intern

Salesforce

Aug 2023 - Oct 2023 (3 months)

- Stayed current on developments in related Python frameworks.
- · Collaborated with quality assurance team to verify correct implementation of software development changes.
- · Handled clerical duties for web development staff to keep department running smoothly.
- Studied user requirements to gain strong understanding of project initiatives and deadlines

Intern

Webstack Academy - WSA

Aug 2023 - Sep 2023 (2 months)

- Analyzed problems and worked with teams to develop solutions.
- · Developed user interfaces with modern JavaScript frameworks, HTML5, and CSS3.
- Wrote custom HTML and JavaScript for existing websites.
- Handled clerical duties for web development staff to keep department running smoothly.
- Studied user requirements to gain strong understanding of project initiatives and deadlines

Education

Sri Indu College Of Engineering & Technology

2020 - 2024



Sri Chaitanya College of Education

intermediate, MPC May 2018 - May 2020



Kendriya vidyalaya

school

Licenses & Certifications

MERN Stack developer - Webstack Academy - WSA WMSI23_001



Salesforce Certifications - SmartInternz

SISFVIPAD2023 -67694

Skills

Engineering • English • Communication • Express.js • MongoDB • HTML5 • Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) • JavaScript • Python (Programming Language)

Honors & Awards

WSA BADGE - Webstack Academy - WSA Aug 2023